[♪ opening theme song playing]
Hang on.
I know Kikuchi said
figuring out
the joker's position
would let him win,
but is that really the case?
Seems kinda arbitrary.
Like for this hand,
Akiyama cuts second,
so the chances of drawing
the joker are even, right?
That's right, more or less.
At the very least,
he didn't draw the joker
-from the start.
-I know!
If the joker stays
in the deck,
then Kikuchi's plan falls apart.
No way he can guarantee
he'll get it at that point.
How can that be a sure win?
-There's more to it.
-Huh?
To put it simply, if Kikuchi's
in position to draw first,
then that means Akiyama
has exactly zero chance
of ending up with the joker.
What?
Let's assume that for this hand,
the joker ended up
on top of the deck.
If Kikuchi discards first,
then he's guaranteed to get it.
So in that case,
he has to just focus
on bleeding Akiyama dry.
But what about the other times?
[DEALER] With that, we'll move
on to the discard phase.
Mr. Kikuchi?
Let's see. I think I'll discard
five this time.
Why is he dumping
his entire hand?
Because the joker
is the fifth card
down in the deck.
-[gasps]
-You see it now?
As long as the joker's
somewhere in the top five cards,
it may as well have been
in Kikuchi's hand
from the beginning.
That's all well and good
if it's high in the deck,
but if it's six
or seven cards down,
couldn't Akiyama
wind up with it?
Not necessarily.
In this game,
you'll always have something
in your first hand,
and the worst
it can be is a pair.
So it's extremely unlikely
that Akiyama will discard
more than three cards per hand.
[NISHIDA] Oh, okay.
With no reason
to expect Akiyama
to ask for more than
three cards,
all Kikuchi needs is one or two.
That way, neither of them
ends up with the joker.
So really, it doesn't matter
where the joker is.
Akiyama's chances
of getting it are nil.
Whereas Kikuchi's
are overwhelming.
That's why he's going to win.
Yeah, sure. But isn't scrapping
his whole hand still risky?
Not in the slightest.
Akiyama made sure of that
by taking two cards last draw.
Because now all 17 cards
in the deck have been in play.
-[NISHIDA] So?
-[KOSAKA] Out of those 17,
ten have passed through
Kikuchi's hand.
And through process
of elimination,
he can deduce which cards
-Akiyama was dealt this hand.
-[NISHIDA] Oh!
And of those cards,
the best hand
he could possibly make
would be two pair,
which Kikuchi can defeat easily.
[NISHIDA] Oh.
[DEALER] Open!
All right!
[SOLARIO] With three of a kind,
Kikuchi wins the hand.
And 20 chips
go to the Western Army.
[Nao gasps]
[DEALER] The fifth hand
will now begin.
Look, he got the joker,
which makes four of a kind.
[DEALER] The first bet
is yours, Mr. Kikuchi.
[KIKUCHI] You know what?
I'm gonna fold.
[Nao gasps]
[SOLARIO] And with that,
the fifth hand is incomplete.
The five-chip antes
go to the dealer,
while the chip balance
remains unchanged.
Really? We had
such a good hand, though.
And why fold?
All that did was remove chips
out of the game.
What was that?
Akiyama started out
with the joker in his hand.
Folding right out of the gate
minimizes our losses.
And furthermore, it sets him up
to cut second in the next hand.
So now he can manipulate
the deck
to get the joker
in his opening hand.
Well, that's good.
There it is.
Incredible.
[DEALER] That concludes
this round of betting.
Now then...
Open!
Oh, yeah!
[SOLARIO] The Western Army
wins with four of a kind.
That's 20 chips directly
into their war chest,
putting them in the lead by 18.
[NAO] What?!
[Kikuchi chuckles]
The Core match
is as good as ours!
-[AKIYAMA] I see you.
-Hmm?
You're following the joker.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
What's ridiculous is
how obvious you are.
A neon sign would be
more subtle.
Drawing four cards
in the practice round.
Discarding your whole hand
in the fourth.
And then the first time
I start off with the Joker,
you fold.
There can be
only one clear explanation
for your behavior.
You know exactly
where the joker is at all times.
That's stupid.
And impossible.
How can I know
where any one card is?
We play with a new deck
each hand.
I think you must be
imagining things.
But then,
it's natural to get jumpy
when you're on the back foot.
[smirks] Jumpy.
Yeah, sure,
that must be what it is.
Timeout!
[SOLARIO] The Eastern Army calls
a timeout for this hand.
You have three minutes
to confer, starting now.
Looks like you're not alone.
Guess it must be
something in the air.
[door slides open]
So is this thing
in the bag or what?
[KIKUCHI] Possibly.
Akiyama's somehow figured out
that I'm keeping track
of where the joker is.
Should we be worried?
Of course not.
Doesn't matter if he knows.
There's nothing
he can do about it.
Because I'm the only one
who can use my trick.
-[NAO] Sorry to intrude.
-Mm?
What is going on here?
So, I want to propose a truce.
-What?
-A truce?
Please listen. I swear,
we want to save you.
Whatever this is,
the answer's no.
Wait, let's hear her out.
I'm curious.
Let me explain.
We chose to finish
the Spearhead match in a tie.
Do you know why we did that?
Because for us to win,
we would have had to pass,
and that would have meant
sacrificing a lot of chips
from both our pools
to the dealer.
Which would shrink
the total pot...
Hurting all of us
in the long run. Do you see?
What are you talking about,
"total pot"?
[NAO] The LGT office handed us
900 million in chips,
but they said they'd
only be collecting six.
That leaves 300 million
on the table for us to win.
That money can save
multiple people,
but we need to work together
to get all of it.
If you agree to concede
this revival round to us,
we swear we'll use that money
to free you all
from the Liar Game!
-[NISHIDA] Uh?
-What a load of bull.
No, I think she means it.
They did go for a draw
in the Spearhead match
after all.
You're buying this?
I don't know why
they caused a draw,
but I know this much...
Self-sabotage
never saved anyone!
But we can!
Nao, stop.
You tried making your pitch,
but they're not going for it.
But still...
[SOLARIO] Your brief
intermission is now over.
Both players,
please return to the table.
-[KIKUCHI] Question.
-Hmm?
Was any of that Kanzaki girl's
babbling believable?
Are you really attempting
to save all of us?
[AKIYAMA] Yes.
If I'm being honest,
that doesn't sound too bad.
[gasps] You hear that?
We're one step closer
to making a truce with them.
[chuckles]
[DEALER]
Mr. Kikuchi, your first bet.
[KIKUCHI] I think I'll go
with a maximum of 15 chips.
[DEALER] Mr. Akiyama,
how will you respond?
[KIKUCHI] Well, you're going
to call, right?
You said you wanted to save us.
Can't do that if the dealer
gets all those chips.
Guess I'll call.
[Kikuchi laughs]
How considerate of you.
-[Nao gasps]
-Well, isn't that
just a big bushel of red flags.
[DEALER] And for your
second bet, sir?
[KIKUCHI] Hmm...
I'll do the max again
and raise 30 chips.
[DEALER] Mr. Akiyama?
[KIKUCHI] I think we all know
where this is going.
[inhales]
Here, I'm gonna help you out
a little bit, 'kay?
Why not?
My cards are such shit,
there's no way
I can win this hand.
So call. You were
never gonna fold anyway.
I call.
[SOLARIO] Astounding.
The pot is now
a whopping 50 chips.
But who will claim it?
[DEALER] Players...
Open!
[SOLARIO] With four queens,
Kikuchi of the Western Army
claims the pot.
[both gasp]
[Kikuchi chuckles]
Like I'd ever allow myself
to end up with a bunk hand.
Not that I was worried,
since the joker was
the second card down.
Of course, I always know
where the joker is,
which is why I'm invincible
in this game.
You did this,
you bleeding heart.
You had to tell them
we were trying
to keep chips away
from the dealer.
And now they're armed
with the knowledge
that Akiyama
can't possibly fold.
But I was...
[SOLARIO] We end this hand
with the Western Army
fifty chips richer.
Putting them 118 chips ahead.
With only three hands left,
is it over for the Eastern Army?
[AKIYAMA] I graciously
called your bet,
knowing full well that you'd
walk away with the pot,
and you mock me for it?
All right then, man.
Just know you brought this down
upon yourself.
[DEALER] We'll now move on
to our eighth hand.
[AKIYAMA] Hold on, please.
You have been letting
the cards show.
[DEALER] Ah!
And furthermore,
Kikuchi's been exploiting that
to memorize the card order
while you shuffle.
I have not.
You're only saying that because
I'm beating you so badly.
[AKIYAMA] I'm saying it
'cause it's true.
You've made it painfully clear
that you know
the joker's location.
-Wait, is he serious?
-[gasps]
These games are fair,
aren't they?
That's what you've told us.
[DEALER]
We strive for that, yes.
Doing only the riffle shuffle
should solve the issue.
That way,
Kikuchi can't follow the cards
since they'll all be face down
on the table.
I'm sure you'd be
agreeable to that.
Prove your innocence
and whatnot.
Very well, then.
If it'll make you feel better,
let's go for it.
Great. Then you may continue.
[Kikuchi scoffs] What an idiot.
The dealer can do
whatever shuffle he wants.
It won't stop my plan.
In fact, the joke's on you
because the riffle shuffle
is easier to follow
than a Hindu.
This is the last bit of kindness
I'll give you.
From here on,
the gloves are coming off.
I'm going to destroy you.
That right?
Trying to get
under my skin, huh?
Then do your worst
because no matter what you do,
I'm still going to win!
♪
Looks like the joker
is the fourth card down.
[DEALER]
Your first bet, if you would.
[KIKUCHI] I need to make sure
he stays in the game.
Which he'll more than likely do
if he thinks I have a bad hand.
So I'll start off small.
Five chips.
Really? Just five?
[DEALER] And for you, sir?
The max sounds good.
I'll do 15 chips.
[all gasp]
[DEALER] Your response?
I will call.
I knew I could keep him
in the game,
but I didn't expect him
to bet the max.
[DEALER] Does anyone have cards
to discard?
[KIKUCHI] Obviously,
he won't discard
more than three.
So I can sit back
and let the joker come to me.
Yes, I'll do all five.
[KIKUCHI] No way!
Now that stupid,
sneaky jerk has the joker!
[DEALER] And how many cards
for you, Mr. Kikuchi?
[KIKUCHI] Just one, please.
Hmm, this is actually
a really good hand.
Akiyama's
still a problem, though.
[DEALER] Your second bet,
Mr. Akiyama.
[KIKUCHI] If he goes big,
then I'll have to fold.
Think I'll just do 15 again.
[KIKUCHI] Huh?
Wait, is that all?
Maybe his hand's not so hot.
Wow, I really lucked out.
-[DEALER] Mr. Kikuchi.
-[KIKUCHI] Hmm.
I call.
[DEALER] Very good. Open!
[SOLARIO]
And with four of a kind,
the East triumphs over the West.
What?
[SOLARIO] With that, Akiyama has
broken Kikuchi's winning streak.
And brought the West's lead
down to 48 chips.
That was incredible.
[KIKUCHI] It's fine.
I knew I'd lose
one or two hands.
Actually,
it's better that I lost,
because now I get to cut second.
And that'll make it much easier
to ensure I get the joker.
More than that,
now I'll be able to guarantee
that the joker ends up
in my opening hand.
Which means there is
no possible way for me to lose!
[DEALER] We'll now begin
our penultimate hand.
All right, it's time
to lock it in.
[Kikuchi laughs]
Sure, whatever you say!
It's too late, but I'll hang
with you for a bit this hand.
[DEALER]
I'll now deal the cards.
[AKIYAMA]
Sorry to be annoying.
But I noticed Kikuchi got a peek
at the cards
while you were shuffling.
Could you please
shuffle them again?
Can we just play the game?
[DEALER] Do you object,
Mr. Kikuchi?
[Kikuchi grunts]
I didn't expect him
to harp on me like this,
but if I object,
I'll look like a cheater,
which will just make
more problems for me.
Not at all.
[DEALER] Is that satisfactory?
Very. Thank you.
[DEALER]
Wonderful. And the cut, sir?
Let's say, five cards.
Four cards, please.
It's all coming together.
That cut put the joker
right where I want it.
Since he cut first,
Akiyama will be dealt in first,
which puts the joker
squarely into my hand.
And that gives me three aces!
Too good!
[DEALER] Would you start us off,
Mr. Akiyama?
[AKIYAMA] Hmm.
I'm gonna check.
[KIKUCHI] He's gonna what?!
Oh, I know what you're doing.
Making me go first
to feel out my hand.
Well, then, feel this out.
Eight chips.
Just eight?
Figured you'd go bigger.
All right.
I'll call.
[KIKUCHI] That's right, idiot!
Take the bait!
[DEALER] Do you wish to discard,
Mr. Kikuchi?
Yes. Two cards, please.
[laughs]
Full house! Aces full of jacks!
I'm unstoppable!
[DEALER] Mr. Akiyama?
[AKIYAMA] Hmm...
Know what? I'll take five.
[KIKUCHI] He's dumping
his whole hand?
What is going on?
Is he spiraling
that badly already?
[DEALER] Mr. Kikuchi,
it's your turn to start us off.
[KIKUCHI]
I'm in a prime position
to finish him off.
But to do that,
I need to make sure
he calls my bet.
And to do that,
I have to convince him
that my hand is utter trash.
I'll just do eight again.
That's interesting.
[DEALER] And you, Mr. Akiyama?
All right, I'll raise.
Let's do the 30-chip maximum.
[Kikuchi screams]
[AKIYAMA] Hm?
[KIKUCHI]
This guy's a grade A moron!
He's so convinced
my hand is terrible
that he went all in.
I don't think I've met
a bigger rube in my entire life!
[DEALER] Your response,
Mr. Kikuchi?
Hmm. I've got no choice.
Guess I have to call.
Oh, this is gonna be so good.
[DEALER] With that,
we move to finish this hand
with an impressive 43 chips
on the table.
Ready?
Open!
[KIKUCHI] Die, Akiyama!
[Kikuchi gasps]
[screaming]
[SOLARIO] Akiyama takes the pot.
Way to go!
[SOLARIO] The Eastern Army
has done the improbable.
However, only our final hand
will determine ultimate victory.
-[Akiyama chuckles]
-[KIKUCHI] That was luck.
Pure, stupid, dumb luck!
He can't do it again.
There's no way
he'll draw four of a kind
on a five-card draw this hand.
And since I lost again,
I'll be cutting the deck second.
Which means in the final hand,
I'll get the joker
right out of the gate!
Mark my words, Akiyama.
You will lose!
[DEALER] Welcome, players,
to the beginning
of our final hand.
[KIKUCHI] Now, of course,
the question isn't if I can win.
It's if he's gonna fold
and end the game,
or ride it out.
-[AKIYAMA] Hey, don't worry.
-Uh?
I'll see this through
to the end.
-[gasps]
-[AKIYAMA] You're surprised?
I could see the concern
on your face.
You're scared that
since I'm winning,
I'll just fold
and end the match. Am I right?
I could, as we could've
in the Spearhead match.
But we didn't cut and run then,
and I won't now.
Because the important thing
isn't eking out a win
however you can.
It's securing enough cash
to survive a loss
in the Liar Game overall.
And right now,
momentum's on my side.
I expect to win,
so I'm setting myself up
for a big windfall.
[KIKUCHI] Oh, you've really
got yourself convinced, huh?
[muffled giggling]
More power to you, you moron.
♪
The joker is the ninth card
from the top.
-[AKIYAMA] Sorry.
-Uh?
One last thing.
This is the final hand,
so let's leave no room
for doubt.
Please shuffle the deck
three more times.
Are you se--
No, fine. Let's do it.
If that's what
it's going to take
to ease your mind.
It is.
All right,
shuffle them again.
[DEALER] Very well, then.
[cards shuffling]
[DEALER] Now to cut the deck...
Mr. Akiyama?
Let's see. Eight cards.
Seven for me, please.
And that will put the joker
sixth from the top of the deck.
Which will ensure it ends up
in my opening hand!
Aces full of kings!
This is perfect!
I don't have
to discard anything!
Question now is...
Will Akiyama make good
on his word to stay in the game?
[DEALER]
It's your bet, Mr. Akiyama.
[AKIYAMA] Hmm.
I'll do 15 chips.
Fifteen?
I told you. I believe I can win,
so I won't be holding back.
[KIKUCHI] That's more like it!
His gambler brain is making him
even stupider than before!
He's gonna lose so much money!
[DEALER] Mr. Kikuchi?
Right, well.
I am pretty far behind.
I guess I'll have to call then.
[DEALER] Very good.
You may now discard.
-Mr. Akiyama?
-Yeah...
I'm gonna discard my whole hand.
[yelps]
You good?
[KIKUCHI] What?
Oh, yes. So good.
This guy went all in
on a garbage hand.
No, that can't be it.
Maybe he thinks
the joker is still in the deck,
and he's desperately trying
to get it.
Oh, well.
Too bad I already made sure
it'd find its way to me!
Still, makes things tricky.
There are only two cards left,
and you only draw one
if you have the joker.
But if I draw two,
we'll have gone through
the whole deck,
and he'll know I have it.
Seems like no matter what I do,
I'll be showing my hand,
as it were.
And he'll fold immediately
after that.
Wait, what if I do nothing?
It's so simple.
I keep my hand
and then just pretend
like the joker is still
one of the remaining cards
in the deck.
Your whole hand again, huh?
Well, then...
These lousy cards
might stand a chance after all.
[AKIYAMA] Hm?
Here goes.
I am keeping my hand.
Besides, it's not like
the odds of my improving
on it now are any good.
Guess I could try,
but that would just give you
another reason to fold, so...
I won't!
Instead, I'll risk it all
on this garbage!
I can't tell if he bought it.
Oh, no!
Did I lay it on too thick?
[DEALER] Let's move on
to the second round of betting.
Mr. Akiyama, if you would.
[KIKUCHI] Stay in!
Stay in, stay in, stay in!
Huh.
I know.
The max, 30 chips.
[Kikuchi squeals]
Sorry, could you repeat that?
Hmm? Yeah, I said 30.
Couldn't see a reason
to play it safe.
Oh, I see.
I won.
By the power
of my acting, I won.
[DEALER] And for your bet,
Mr. Kikuchi?
I'll call. It's only fair.
[DEALER] Very good.
The hand is now complete.
[Kikuchi chuckles]
[laughs]
Yes! And that's the game!
You just got played, Akiyama!
I what?
You got played!
And now that the hand's over,
I'm gonna tell you how!
You see, you were right.
I knew!
I've known where the joker was
for most of the game!
I've won.
And you never saw it coming!
[laughing]
[♪ closing theme song playing]